Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.twelve Mss.B.B61.inventory12
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents S
  - Sturtevant, E. H. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 May 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Sep. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 26; 1p
  - Subscription News Co. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1898 Oct. 15
  - Succo, Reinh (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1886 Apr. 7
  - Suckey, J. C. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1890 June 7; 1p
  - Sudenadel, C. W. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 28
  - Suess, Eduard (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1885 Nov. 14
  - Sujamain, C. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1930 June 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 May 24; 2p
  - Sullivan, John (Box 87)
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 19; 1p
  - Sullivan, Louis R. (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1919 May 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 July 14; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Sep. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Sep. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 27; 2p
  - Sulzberger, A. H. (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 9; 1p
  - "The Sun" (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 20
  - Sunday Times Magazine (Box 87)
    See Markel, Lester
  - Sunmer, Dwight (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 27; 3p
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 3; 2p
  - Sunrise Club (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 11; 1p
  - Supan, A. (Box 87)
    - To Boas, 1884 Oct. 10
    - To Boas, 1888 Jan. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1888 Jan. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1888 May 8; 3p
    - To Boas, 1888 Oct. 1; 3p
    - To Boas, 1888 Dec. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1890 Jan. 16; 2p
    - To Pertues Geographische Austalt, 1884 Dec. 23
  - Surette, Thomas Whitney (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1927 May 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 May 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 June 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Sep. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 May 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 May 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 June 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 May 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 May 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 June 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 May 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 31; 1p
  - Survey Association (Box 87)
    See Survey Graphic
    See Weybright, Victor
    See Keely, Paul
  - Survey Graphic (Box 87)
    See Survey Associates
  - Susman, Amelia (Box 87)
    Tsimshian
    - From Boas, 1937 July 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 May 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 May 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 20; 1p
    - Enc: List of Beynon notebooks sent to Dr. Susman, 1939 Dec. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec.
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Aug. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Sep. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 May 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 July 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Aug. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 May 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 May 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 May 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 July 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 July 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 July 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 June 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 June 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 21; 4p
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Sep. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Sep. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Nov. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 4; 1p
    - Found at end of Dec. 1939, 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 8
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 22; 3p
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 25
    - To Boas, 1940 Apr. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Apr. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 June 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 June 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 June 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 July 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 July 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 Aug. 5
    - E, 1940 Aug. 10; 1p
    - Enc. with Susman, A., 1940 Aug. 10
    - To Boas, 1940 Aug. 12; 1p
    - See Boas, F. (open letter), 1940 Sep. 24
    - To Boas, 1940 Sep. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Nov.; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Apr. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1941 May 3; 3p
    - To Boas, 1941 May 28; 1p
    - See Hockett, Charles, 1939 Jan. 30
    - To Edel, B., 1940 Aug. 5
  - Susman, Mrs. Esther (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1939 July 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 12; 2p
  - Sussman, Esther B. (Box 87)
    - To Boas, 1937 Aug. 20; 1p
  - Sussman, S. (Box 87)
    - To Boas, 1918 May 6; 1p
  - Sutherland, Edwin H. (Box 87)
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies, 1938 Jan.
  - Sutherland, R. L. (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 24; 1p
  - Sutphen, F. T. (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1939 Sep. 20; 1p
  - Sutro, Mrs. Lionel (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 4; 1p
    - See letter dated Oct. 4 1933 to Warburg, Mrs. Paul to Boas, F., 1933 Oct. 4; 2p
  - Sütterlin, Z. (Box 87)
    - To Boas, 1895 Jan. 31; 4p
    - To Boas, 1895 Nov. 20
    - To Boas, 1895 Nov. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1896 Mar. 4
  - Sutton, James E. (Box 87)
    - To Boas, 1891 Jan. 8
  - Sutton, William J. (Box 87)
    - To Boas, 1888 Nov. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1889 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1889 May 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1889 July 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1890 May 22; 1p
  - Suzzalle, Henry (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1922 Oct. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 27; 1p
  - Sverdrup, George (Box 87)
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 31
  - Swadesh, Morris -- See also Haas, Mary R. (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 29; 1p
    - Enc. Boas, F. (open letter), 1937 May 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 May 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 June 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 June 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 July 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Aug. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Sep. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 22
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 June 22; 1p
    - See Boas, F. (to Bloomfield, L), 1939 Dec. 12
    - From Boas
    - see Boas, F. (to Comm. on Amer. Indian Linguistics), 1939 Dec. 18
    - See Boas, F. (to Comm. on research on Amer. Indian Languages), 1940 Jan. 16
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 9; 1p
    - See Boas, F. (to Comm. on Native Amer. Languages...Swadesh), 1940 Apr. 29
    - See Boas, F. (toComm. on Native Amer. Languages), 1940 May 31
    - See Boas, F. (to Bloomfield, L.), 1940 July 31
    - From Boas, 1941 Feb. 6; 1p
    - See Boas, F. (to Hoijer, H.), 1941 July 31
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 28; 3p
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 19; 3p
    - See Boas, F. (to Sapir, E.), 1937 May 3
    - To Boas, 1937 May 22; 1p
    - From Townsend, W.C., 1937 May 25
    - To Boas, 1937 May 29; 1p
    - Enc: Bulletin, 1937 June 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 July 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 July 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Aug. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 1; 1p
    - Enc. Plan for the financing of a Journal for American Indian Linguistics, 1938 Feb. 8
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Aug. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 6; 1p
    - See Boas, F. (to Swadesh, M.), 1938 Nov. 29
    - See Boas, F. (to Kroeber, A.L.), 1939 Jan. 5
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 9; 1p
    - See Rubin de la Borbolla, D.F., 1939 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1939 May 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 June 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Aug. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Dec. 18; 2p
    - From Andrade, M.J., 1937 July 11
    - From Edel, B.C.-See Edel, B.C. (to Cowan, J.M., 1942 Dec. 30
    - See Edel, B.C. (to Bloomfield, L.), 1943 Jan. 6
    - From Kroeber, A.L., 1940 Jan. 19
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 25
    - To Bloomfield, L., 1937 Oct. 22; 1p
    - on margin: Bloomfield, L., 1937 Oct. 25; 2p
  - Swan, James G. (Box 87)
    - To Boas, 1890 July 29
  - Swanton, Alice B. (Box 87)
    - To Boas, 1904 Jan. 13; 3p
  - Swanton, John R. (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1899 June 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1899 June 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1899 Aug. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1899 Aug. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 4
    - From Boas, 1903 Dec. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Apr. 5; 2p
    - From Boas, 1904 Oct. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Oct. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Oct. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Oct. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Oct. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Nov. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Nov. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Dec. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Dec. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Dec. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Dec. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 Feb. 3
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 29
    - From Boas, 1905 June 5
    - From Boas, 1905 June 6
    - From Boas, 1905 June 9
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 4
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 10
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 28
    - From Boas, 1906 July 19
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 3
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 22
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 26
    - From Boas, 1907 May 7
    - From Boas, 1907 May 21
    - From Boas, 1907 May 27
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 10
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 27
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 4
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 5
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 13
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 25; 3p
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 2; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 6
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 28
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 13
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 25
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 25
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 19
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 1
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 22
    - From Boas, 1909 May 8
    - From Boas, 1909 May 26
    - From Boas, 1909 May 27
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 16
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 30
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 5
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 13
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 11
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 1
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 12
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 15
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 18; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 May 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Jan. 15; 4p
    - From Boas, 1920 Jan. 21; 3p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 May 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 May 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Sep. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 May 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 May 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 June 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Sep. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 June 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 July 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 June 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Feb. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 May 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 May 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 May 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 July 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Apr. 9; 1p
    - To Tozzer, A.M. & Swanton, J.R., 1909 Apr. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1898 Mar. 17; 3p
    - To Boas, 1899 June 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1899 June 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1899 July 14; 3p
    - To Boas, 1899 July 22; 5p
    - To Boas, 1899 July 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1899 Aug. 22; 4p
    - To Boas, 1899 Sep.; 4p
    - To Boas, 1899 Sep. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1901 May 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1902 Feb. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1902 Dec. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Jan. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Jan. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Feb. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Feb. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Feb. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Feb. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Feb. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Apr. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1903 May 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 June 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 16; 8p
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Jan. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Jan. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1904 Oct. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Dec. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 2
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 31
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 29
    - To Boas, 1905 May 31
    - To Boas, 1905 June 7
    - To Boas, 1905 July 18
    - To Boas, 1905 July 20
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 3
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 19
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 8
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1906 July 2
    - To Boas, 1906 July 16
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1907 May 4
    - To Boas, 1907 June 10
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 3
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 4
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 27
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 27
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 16
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 15
    - To Boas, 1909 May 29
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 20
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 7
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 15
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 2
    - To Boas, 1910 May 7
    - To Boas, 1910 May 27
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 9
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 12
    - To Boas, 1914 May 25
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 16
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 June 29
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 3; 6p
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 9
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 6; 4p
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 20; 3p
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 May 19; 3p
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 May 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 May 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Jan. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Jan. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Jan. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 June 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Apr. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Apr. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Jan. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 May 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 June 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 June 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Sep. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 July 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 July 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Feb. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 May 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 May 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 May 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 May 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Feb. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Mar. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Apr. 10; 1p
    - To Miss Andrews, 1903 Jan. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 June 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1903 June 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1903 June 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 30; 1p
    - From Andrews, H. A., 1907 Oct. 7
    - To Frachtenberg, 1917 Nov. 3
    - To Dept. Of Justice (U.S.), 1917 Nov. 1; 3p
  - Swartout, M. (Box 87)
    - To Boas, 1903 June 22; 1p
  - Sweden, Minister (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 18; 1p
  - Swedes, Emilie R. (Box 87)
    - To Boas, 1901 Dec. 13
  - Swenson C. (Box 87)
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 8
  - Swetlow (Box 87)
    See Boas, F. (to Anon.)
    - Found at end of Dec. 1928
  - Swett, Otis D. (Box 87)
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 27; 1p
  - Swift, A.L., Jr. (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1940 June 10; 1p
  - Swindlehurst, F. (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 18
  - Switzerland, Consulate General of (Box 87)
    See Rosset, Charles E.
  - Swope, H. B. (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 19; 1p
  - Sydenstricker, E. (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 7; 1p
  - Sydow, B. V. (Box 87)
    - To Boas, 1934 Sep. 5
  - Sydow, C. M. von (Box 87)
    - To Germany. Reichs-u Preussischen Minister für Wissenschaft Erziehung und Volksbildung
    - Enc. with Sydow, C.M., 1935 Mar. 1
  - Sydow, C. W. von (Box 87)
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 1; 1p
  - Sydow, E. von (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1934 July 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Sep. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 June 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 June 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 July 14; 2p
  - Sykes, F. H. (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1903 May 2; 2p
    - From Boas, 1903 May 2; 2p
    - From Boas, 1903 May 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 May 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 May 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 May 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 May 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 May 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1903 May 19; 1p
    - Symbolic Movement (See also Gesture)
      - Attached to letter to George W. Cohen, dated 8-20-36
  - Symonds, B. (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 25
  - Sywulka, Edward F. (Box 87)
    - To Sapir, E., 1937 July 14; 1p
  - Szilard, Leo (Box 87)
    - To Boas, 1933 May
    - Enc: Szilard, L(to Breit, G.), 1933 May
    - To Beveridge, W., 1933 May 4; 2p
    - Enc. with Liebowitz, B. (to Boas, E.P.), 1933 May 4
    - To Breit, G., 1933 May; 2p
    - Enc. with Szilard, L., 1933 May
    - To Marschak, 1933 May 9; 3p
    - From Rosenfeld, L., 1933 Apr. 24
    - Enc. with Liebowitz, B. (to Boas, E.B.), 1933 May 4
    - From Rosenfeld, L., 1933 May 2
    - Enc. with Liebowitz, B. (to Boas, E.P.), 1933 May 4
    - From Schlesinger, K., 1933 May 2
    - Enc. with Liebowitz, B., 1933 May 4
      (to Boas, E.P.)
    - To Schlesinger, K., 1933 May 9; 3p